var quizQuestions = [{
    "sub_skill": "String Handling",
    "question": "Which of the following are incorrect form of StringBuffer class constructor?",
    "answers": [{
            "option": "StringBuffer(String str)"
        },
        {
            "option": "StringBuffer(int size , String str)"
        },
        {
            "option": "StringBuffer(int size)"
        },
        {
            "option": "StringBuffer()"
        }
    ],
    "correct": "StringBuffer(String str)",
    "difficulty level": "Medium",
    "mark": 1
}, {
    "sub_skill": "String Handling",
    "question": "Which of these operators can be used to concatenate two or more String objects?",
    "answers": [{
            "option": "+="
        },
        {
            "option": "&"
        },
        {
            "option": "+"
        },
        {
            "option": "||"
        }
    ],
    "correct": "+",
    "difficulty level": "Medium",
    "mark": 1
}, {
    "sub_skill": "String Handling",
    "question": "Which of these method of class String is used to extract a substring from a String object?",
    "answers": [{
            "option": "SubString()"
        },
        {
            "option": "Substring()"
        },
        {
            "option": "None of the mentioned"
        },
        {
            "option": "substring()"
        }
    ],
    "correct": "substring()",
    "difficulty level": "Medium",
    "mark": 1
}, {
    "sub_skill": "Recursion",
    "question": "What is Recursion in Java?",
    "answers": [{
            "option": "Recursion is a process of defining a method that calls other methods repeatedly"
        },
        {
            "option": "Recursion is a process of defining a method that calls other methods which in turn call again this method"
        },
        {
            "option": "Recursion is a class"
        },
        {
            "option": "Recursion is a process of defining a method that calls itself repeatedly"
        }
    ],
    "correct": "Recursion is a process of defining a method that calls other methods repeatedly",
    "difficulty level": "Low",
    "mark": 1
}, {
    "sub_skill": "Inheritance",
    "question": "Which of these keyword can be used in subclass to call the constructor of superclass?",
    "answers": [{
            "option": "super"
        },
        {
            "option": "this"
        },
        {
            "option": "extends"
        },
        {
            "option": "extent"
        }
    ],
    "correct": "super",
    "difficulty level": "Low",
    "mark": 1
}, {
    "sub_skill": "Objects",
    "question": "Which of these method of Object class can clone an object?",
    "answers": [{
            "option": "Object clone()"
        },
        {
            "option": "clone()"
        },
        {
            "option": "copy()"
        },
        {
            "option": "Objectcopy()"
        }
    ],
    "correct": "Object clone()",
    "difficulty level": "Low",
    "mark": 1
}, {
    "sub_skill": "Objects",
    "question": "Which of these is wrapper for simple data type char?",
    "answers": [{
            "option": "String"
        },
        {
            "option": "Character"
        },
        {
            "option": "Integer"
        },
        {
            "option": "Float"
        }
    ],
    "correct": "Character",
    "difficulty level": "Low",
    "mark": 1
}, {
    "sub_skill": "String Handling",
    "question": "Which of these method of class String is used to check whether a given object starts with a particular string literal?",
    "answers": [{
            "option": "endsWith()"
        },
        {
            "option": "Starts()"
        },
        {
            "option": "ends()"
        },
        {
            "option": "startsWith()"
        }
    ],
    "correct": "startsWith()",
    "difficulty level": "Low",
    "mark": 1
}, {
    "sub_skill": "Inheritance",
    "question": "A class member declared protected becomes member of subclass of which type?",
    "answers": [{
            "option": "public member"
        },
        {
            "option": "protected member"
        },
        {
            "option": "private member"
        },
        {
            "option": "static member"
        }
    ],
    "correct": "private member",
    "difficulty level": "Medium",
    "mark": 1
}, {
    "sub_skill": "Inheritance",
    "question": "A class member declared protected becomes member of subclass of which type?",
    "answers": [{
            "option": "public member"
        },
        {
            "option": "protected member"
        },
        {
            "option": "private member"
        },
        {
            "option": "static member"
        }
    ],
    "correct": "private member",
    "difficulty level": "Medium",
    "mark": 1
}];


export default quizQuestions;